### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/thiennguyen-72b163258 (LinkedIn) www.behance.net/thinquang (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Prototyping
Mockups
User Interviews

### Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

UX Writing Basic to Advanced UXUI Web/Mobile App Product Design

Hi-fi Prototype: UX/UI Motion Design

Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate

Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes in Figma

# Thien Nguyen

Junior UX/UI Designer at Nimble Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

# Summary

Hi there!

This is Thien and I am on my journey to get myself ready to become a great UI/UX designer, hoping that my little work could bring outstanding experience to many users out there.

Looking forward to learning more from you guys!

# Experience

Nimble

Junior UX/UI Designer November 2023 - Present (1 year 5 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Wall Street English Vietnam
Senior Personal Academic Coach
September 2016 - April 2022 (5 years 8 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Delivered academic support to students.
- · Conducted classes, advising sessions, and speaking clubs.
- Followed up with students closely to make sure they are highly engaged and achieving their learning goals.
- Collaborated with Educational Consultants to facilitate renewals and referrals.
- Was an event coordinator and had a lot of successful big events with a large number of students and prospects attending (Oktoberfest, World Environment Day, Halloween Party,...)
- Supported Center Head of Coaching to manage Platinum students' schedules
- · Conducted End of Course training for new coaches

## Education

Coursera

Google UX Design Professional Certificate (Online) (2023 - 2023)

Keyframe Multimedia School
UI/UX Product Design Completed · (2022 - 2023)

Vietnam Aviation Academy
Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and
Management, General · (2013 - 2016)